<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PlanMyTrip</string>
    <string name="australia_description">Australia\'s spectacular natural environment, multicultural communities, excellent food and wine, its weather and lifestyle and the friendliness and openness of its people make it one of the world\'s most attractive tourist destinations.</string>
    <string name="bali_description">Bali Island is a small beautiful island and a part of Indonesia archipelago, and the most famous of Indonesian tourism in the world. It owns the panorama and unique culture that make this island is exclusive than others. Furthermore, It\'s location is in the tropical situation as Dream Island for a vacation.</string>
    <string name="dubai_description">Dubai is famous for contemporary sightseeing attractions such as the Burj Khalifa (the world\'s tallest building) and shopping malls that come complete with mammoth aquariums and indoor ski slopes. But this city has many cultural highlights and things to do, as well as all the glamorous modern add-ons.</string>
    <string name="france_description">France is one of the oldest nations on Earth and the most ethnically diverse country in Europe. These deep and broad influences have made France a world leader throughout history in nearly all aspects of culture, including cuisine, wine-making, politics, philosophy, music, art, film, fashion, literature, and sports.</string>
    <string name="india_description">India is a country that attracts millions of tourists every year and is considered one of the most popular tourist destinations in the world. These visitors are attracted to its natural beauty and cultural heritage. It has many historic sites as well like the Taj Mahal, Golden Temple, Red Fort, etc.</string>
    <string name="italy_description">It has beautiful scenery ranging from its scenic coastal areas to its colourful mountain ranges. It has a vast wealth of culture, architecture and ancient sites. It has modern cities that embody contemporary Italy, and don\'t forget Italy\'s gifts to the world\'s taste buds, its wonderful cuisine and wines.</string>
    <string name="singapore_description">The exquisitely beautiful attractions like Sentosa Island, Gardens by the Bay, Universal Studios and Night Safari are the pride of Singapore tourism. Singapore is an ideal destination to plan a fun-filled holiday with family. There are a plethora of activities and attractions for your children.</string>
    <string name="china_description">The Great Wall of China, The Forbidden City, Imperial Palace, The Terracotta Army, The Summer Palace, Li River, Guilin, Chengdu Research Base of Giant Panda Breeding, Yangtze River and the Three Gorges and many more.</string>
    <string name="florida_description">World-famous attractions such as Walt Disney World and Universal Studios Florida make Orlando a year-round tourist destination, but there are many attractions and activities outside of the theme parks.</string>
    <string name="canada_description">With so much breathtaking scenery and natural attractions, it\'s no surprise that Canada is known for its incredible hiking opportunities. From longer, more challenging treks to family-friendly day hikes, Canada has a wide array of trails for enjoying the country\'s natural splendor.</string>
    <string name="russia_description">Major tourist routes in Russia include a travel around the Golden Ring of ancient cities, cruises on the big rivers including the Volga, and long journeys on the Trans-Siberian Railway.</string>
    <string name="tokyo_description">Tokyo is known for iconic landmarks like the Tokyo Skytree and Shibuya Crossing. It\'s famous for its sakura tree-lined streets, shrines and temples, its otaku culture and wonderful cuisine, and its world-class transport system.</string>
    <string name="turkey_description">Historic ruins, bustling cities, beautiful beaches, mountains, shopping, excellent food, and all at an affordable price. So whatever you\'re looking for, be it a short city trip to Istanbul, a beach holiday along the south coast, or a place to travel for a while with a mix of everything, Turkey could be for you.</string>
</resources>